I thought of doing some proper Vipassana
the interrogation self interrogation
then obviously as we spoke before
results can result directly in
establishments of the mind in Samadhi
hence the proper person of self
interrogation would bring forward Somali
composure upon the right things
wholesome themes themes free from greed
aversion and delusion I think pretty one
we done before was kind of a suffering
wasn't feeling in certainty in terms of
quality unwholesome to do the sensuality
or in terms of real world well again
lucky it can be done by anyone to
oneself
so for example right here right now
is there is a sensuality present in in
the background of the mind
is the design although desire for the
one team of some pleasure based upon
sure the census which theories by the
way I can I'm not just asking you I'm
putting the question out but yeah yeah
you could say that is there a desire for
wanting a pleasure on account of sent
spaces which is what enjoy this do I
entertain a possibility it's somehow
well no there will be the further know
for now is there huh
is there a desire for pleasure of the
senses
yes or no just it was generally you need
to look for every little what if notice
overall he's my mind now under the
pressure of sensuality or is my mind now
not under the pressure of sensuality as
the question person should be asking
myself like right here right now yes
because I'm sitting in a comfortable
position okay maintaining good I mean
but that's not sexuality yeah I'm trying
to maintain that whenever it is not
avoiding avoiding discomfort is not
essential necessary central maintain the
comforts no pleasure sensuality it's
basically pleasure of the that you can
gain through the sense basis engaging
with its sensual counterparts lust greed
are you lost for about sitting in a
comfortable chair
yeah you have an option you are you
sitting sometimes gets uncomfortable in
this position but that's not it that's
with me like you have to start
differentiating the type of pleasure
there is unwholesome because welcome
people come see lecture some of the
people will assume you must forsake
everything you know everything every
little didn't know their desires that
are not desires avoiding discomfort is
just intentional for another hunt as
well but I mean lost the vision delusion
sensuality is there is there any as the
way they would say like desired in
regard to the world or sort of
displeasure in regard to the world which
is rooted on the same domain discontent
craving for so that's that's the
question a properly person can start in
my mind right here right now under the
pressure of sensual craving of wanting
the wanting of pleasure pleasure of the
senses so the answer will have to be yes or no
on that general and he's the moment is
when my car in the effectiveness enjoy
as satipatthana stood they would say far
as I can tell them that no no that's
fine so the answer like let's start let's say
so the answer like let's start let's say
the answer is no but I'm not completely
sure that's probably many people who'd
answer it so no but I'm not completely
sure what is not being completely sure
me mean you're not free from doubt in
regard to it and if you're not free from
doubt in regard to a dhama a phenomena
you can't say you're free from it you
can't say you're free from that domain
that's what freedom from doubt for a
soda by it's like the first step towards
the right view but it's the same
principle then that he can develop so
the body is not free from sin Charlie
for example because he's still not free
from doubt in regard to sensual domain
or if the Buddha would say he still
hasn't fully understood the
gratification the danger and the escape
you understand that fully means you
fully won't be on doubt in regard to the
nature of sensuality and that's a fine
starting point so you can say no
currently our mind is not under the
influence of sensuality but I'm not
really sure about so does that mean that
there might be a way that sensuality is
influencing you maybe does that mean the
Marquee away this is surely my inference
well it's basically you recognize that
currently the mind is not under the
pressure of sensuality but you also
simultaneously there simply by saying
I'm not sure means the possibility of
sensuality you recognize you are not
free there could be exactly and that's
the point here to study cernan the
possibility of sensuality that you are
still liable to but that need like you
can't wait for it
to be manifest in the future to deal
with it possibility it has to be dealt
as possibility which means if in the
future the sensuality manifests that's
not the possibility now that you
thinking of sure it came through the
domain of possibility but at that time
in the future you're gonna another
domain a possibility in regard to it
because possibility is a part of that
structure of the main off off of
manifested things things that are
present and its possibilities it's
implicit it's what gives things the
meaning so that's what I mean the
possibility of sensuality that you
implied through the answer the one will
imply if they say no currently I'm not
another present of sensuality but I'm
not quite sure means okay the time will
come when I will be oppressed by
sensuality so that also means that the
reason they are not oppressed now is not
fully understood why why am I not
oppressed now and why I might be
impressed in the future with the next
one that comes but understanding it and
understanding that possibility of
oppression yeah needs to be done in the
present present there is an experience
that now you're having the person about
and that's how you overcome the whole
domain because the root of the domain
central domain domain of anger domain of
unwholesome is not in the particular
manifestation of those the root is you
being liable to the possibility of those
same with suffering
that's where dukkha is not like it not
necessarily the tremendous horrific
torture pain and discomfort it's this is
dukkha is opposite of suka literally
would be to say this this is an ease and
that's that's the nature of human
experience to know that everybody
suffers all the time not at all but
possibility in all the time in human
experience is that of uneasiness that is
implied why because things can at any
given moment in the future so there is a
present possibility of things in the
future at any given moment going not the
you want them to that's where they would
have said fundamentally suffering is
basically being separated from things
you want being United with things you
don't want has in United with feelings
and perceptions you don't want separated
from the ones you want
oh.just misconceiving the father it's
misconceiving the experience as a whole
that's why you suffer and you miss
conceived it as you are the one in
control you're the one in charge but
then every next second when another
thing is manifest it can prove you wrong
and you remain liable to that for a
zombie's us maintained assumption and
you are in charge but if you stop meet
any assumption you're in charge you have
surmounted the domain of possibility of
being proven wrong that you are not in
control wanna come to which you would
suffer
so that only the possibilities must be
understood as possibilities within the
presently enduring experience as a whole
it's not like momentary glimpses of
figuring out or discerning why and how
and working some methodical patterns
none of it there's a simple question and
a simple answer but you need to know
what to look for it and then you get to
see the science of the things that
matter and even mind cutting the
pressure of sensuality no can my mind be
then pressure with sensuality mm-hmm
maybe maybe means yes doubt means yes
okay so my mind can be pressure but
sensuality do I have to wait for that in
the future to prove that yes truly it
was pressured or I already know that
simply by doubting it you already know
it because you don't understand the
nature of that possible pressure you
liable to it and that's just starting
point by the way starting point is
you're liable to that pressure it's not
like a perfect starting point and then
you occasionally petitioner makes
mistakes and then steps back into
sensuality no he's puta Gina not free
from sensuality because he hasn't
understood that domain of possible
pressure of sensuality possible
liability if liability is possible means
overall you are liable not always but
sometimes and sometimes it's enough for
the nature of sensuality to still
pertain to you so if you don't want
nature sensuality still pertain to you
who nature dot on edge of suffering or
nature anger or nature of anything
unwholesome that possibility of pertain
to you needs to be understood and
abandoned right here right now as
possibility needs to be discerned that's
almost about the peripheral awareness
the mindfulness of luck tell that the
science because it's on the level of
signs and tokens of the presently
manifested things as it currently
presently mind is not oppressed by
sensuality but it's signs
it's tokens it's significance is that if
be in the future and that's what binds
you the fact that the mind is currently
pressured or not pressured that's
basically a result of your liability to
the domain in the first place
so in other words you don't need to wait
for it to be pressured to know that you
are pressured you don't need to wait for
it to realize that you are not in
control like to be forced upon you
through like accidents or whatever
things happening just the fact that it
might happen means you're not in control
that's why you don't need to have
anything horrible happen to you in order
to become aware of the dukkha the
fundamental sign of human experience but
it won't be seen on the particular basis
that's already a symptom of your
liability so let's get back to them
presently so there is a possibility
there is a possibility exactly which so
that's it so now people would generally
like what the mind would usually do is
trying to rationalize it but finding out
why or how because of this so because of
that it's all the result of your
liability in the first place to that
possibility of suffering or sensuality
or anger that would have been hit by the
first arrow he doesn't see that he's too
concerned about figuring out who hit him
what's the name of the client from the
man who shot him what's the name of this
who is the surgeon what did he know
that's only relevant what is relevant is
that you were touched in the first place
as it you're liable to it so possibility
of sensuality is something that the mind
is liable to in this present enduring
experiences at all
so you can let it endure or sink in you
okay I need to figure it out start
recognizing the phenomenon of enduring
possibility as a phenomenon for enduring
possibility what is your attitude
towards possibility or sunshine me
anything I want to be kid you won't be
killed okay why do you want to be
careful because I want a possibility to
become next reality you don't want to be
affected by a which you already are and
that's all fine there's no like right or
wrong answer through doing this kind of
interrogation you get to clarify and see
signs and tokens of present the enduring
phenomena present enduring Dhamma and
then the money starts discerned there is
also present enduring down on a more
peripheral level and that's how the mind
gets established upon the right things
upon non-centrality non green on a
version so ask yourself then or whoever
misses witness can ask myself then why
would I be affected by the possibility
of arising of sensuality arising
what would wouldn't be affected maybe
okay so how would I clarify that in the
present not like waiting for thing but
on the level of possibility so let's
assume that you would be affected
because in the past you always were
affected so then you ask yourself why am
i affected while the possibility right
now right right here right now
possibility of enduring possibility of
arising of sensuality arising why am I
liable to it right here right now
possibility well yes but that's clearly
not on you you did not create that
possibility yes okay what are the
characteristics of that possibility
let's verify that angle first body what
are the characteristics of the
possibility of sensuality presently
enduring they are characteristics
described it just in any manner its but
it's connected to the body mystics okay
so if something is separable from the
randomly reason body did you have no
control no smell taste touch and so on
and this is inseparable from it which
means possibility of the sense sense
basis of your body that's what's in
Charlotte is but that also implies it's
kind of stretch of structural as well as
the Buddha said I wants to go and feel
its own domain that's what it does it's
like a wild animal
so the five wild animals deposit their
feeding grounds and the possibilities of
what they could eat that's just how
things are you haven't created that the
body and that's important thing to
discern yeah because people might think
it's on them and then try to prevent
this particular thing to be or that or
if they feel with this I don't know like
of course the restrain is to be before
and you need to restrain the animals in
order to understand the nature of the
feeling ground and how it affects you
but the possibility of i feeding on
sites is the eyes possibility smells
possibility of smells is the nose
possibility possibility of touch or do
the possibility so why does that
possibility then affect you I need you
if I think it is mine exactly
if you appropriated so how do you then
appropriate it what is the necessary
condition for appropriation there the
Buddha said what is the necessary
condition for regarding something as
yours good for me
yeah but why would you regard it as for
why would you accept it
oh okay this for me if I come with that
with a with a gun and a bullet and say
this is for you would you say oh yeah
sure give it to me
shoot me you wouldn't yeah well why cuz
it's unpleasant yeah
so whenever there is appropriation there
is welcoming beforehand that's the
necessary basis there is perceived
pleasure ability of it
that's why sense of self as in the
middle pointed out he's always developed
on the basis of pleasure they study
Buddha says sabi Sankara
Anita sabi sand Cara dukkha you need to
see that which is inseparable from this
thing that you are taking is yours as
actually a pleasure as not wanted
so absolutely true you are affected by
the possibilities of sensuality that
actually pertain to your senses not to
you possibilities are not a problem
they have possibilities problem is when
you start engaging account of the
possibilities when I come in the
pressure of possibilities but you cannot
start engaging with them unless you take
in them as pertaining to you and the
necessary basis for taking anything as
pertaining to you is regarding it as
their pleasurable agreeable
non-threatening hence the Buddha's
insistence constantly talking about the
scene the danger
because that's how you are pruned you
can't just say okay this is not for me
anymore because if still there is the
implication of pleasure ability of it
the assumption for me is automatic so
you undo the assumption for me no per se
okay it's not for me
good luck with that but by actually
seeing it as unpleasurable more
fundamental and then automatically
becomes who not for me
that's the similar of the charcoal pit
where the Buddha said if the two men
with the two strong men would come and
grab you by the arms and drag you
towards and drop you like a hole dug up
full of embers would in your mind want
to be everywhere else except their
intention will be turning
everyone else except wanted to go into
that hole if you start regarding the
possibility of sensual pleasure like
that that's how you stop being liable to
the entire domain
that's how whatever presently
particularly actually arises for your I
know smell taste arches on he will not
induce the sensual domain upon you
that's why the Buddha said to target
that still sees his recognizes beautiful
things in the world but he has no desire
and lust in regard to them because he
freed himself from the assumption of
sensual domain assumption of my sensual
domain assumption of pleasure ability of
my sensual domain then is just agreeable
sight disagreeable sight agreeable
comfortable chair disagreeable this
comfortable chair none of that is
sensuality none of that will be anger
none of there will be suffering
none of there will be a problem and all
like all this just on the basis of
couple of right questions and right
attitude in regard to it and that's what
my personal truly is that's what we
would say he investigates the meaning
luck to himself questions himself or if
he sees somebody who might know more
understand Mori goes and gets himself
interrogated basically because that's
how you you unravel yeah you know these
things to some extent but you really
want to discern them on the basis of the
present and during mindfulness of the
experiences at all and he all what we
talked nothing is the basis hasn't
changed mind is presently not treasured
by any sensuality oh but how about
possibility of it am i fully certain the
free from the extent of sensual domain I
don't know that's your starting point
you don't know means you're not why
aren't you because it doesn't pertain to
you as you just clarified it pertains to
the senses oh because I'm still actually
regarding it is there an agreeable
that's really the say you should regard
your senses and the mind
thinking itself as well like the
assassins like the best friend that you
know comes and gets your trust and then
just wants to kill you at night not like
if you go paranoid all the time just
recognize no I just need to stop
regarding this possibility of sensuality
is not my friend
dangerous perilous charcoal pit burning
and skin disease all the Sooners are
gonna get know everything all the time
miserable hey no just that degree were
your liable good and the possibility is
wearing you're liable to all because of
it so if you stop welcoming that
possibility that pertains to the senses
not to you then that possibility stops
bothering you if the post if you are not
liable to the possibility of sensuality
can you then be liable to anything that
manifests itself through that
possibility of sensuality absolutely no
whatever whatever possibility becomes
possible here now there might be a
possible when you're not thinking about
the particular or future this might be
possible anything about possibility in
its nature yeah
currently I'm not pressured by any
central cravings can I say there will be
the same for the future means but if
there is essential crave America as a
possibility well it won't be a central
cleaning if you freed yourself from the
possibility of sensual claiming like any
particular manifestation of sensuality
say the answer is are you presently
oppressed by central credit the answer
is yes yes my mind is just thinking
about the central object so based on
that okay so can you then say that in
the future you'll be free from sexuality
no because even now you're not freedom
so with the first step what restrain you
don't go for a central object but now
the pressure of it has been revealed
again same questioning why instead of
why would I be pressuring the future
just start with why my pressured now the
product possibility here and now for
engaging you know possibly to engage no
said I'm obsessed with cake and there's
a cake right in front of me
sure so yesterday I said oh there's a
possibility that if I see a cake in the
future I will be pressured to go for it
now today there is a cake in front of me
yeah but that's the thing but I know
that possibility for engaging with it
okay you still there but if I have
surmounted this possibility
yesterday yesterday I'm still cementing
it today even if the cake is presented
oh absolutely absolutely that's the
whole point was reduced oh yeah well no
the cake is presented the possibility is
there but your surmounting with the
possibility didn't end yesterday because
the possibility is not spit its present
enduring right here and now and he was
the same possibility that you had in the
past and with the same possibility
having the future yeah wait a little bit
but suppose the mounting the possibility
you have surmounted your past sensuality
and your surmounting any future
engagement with sensuality and that's
exactly what Buddha said regardless of
what the one who summons the sense of
self correctly sees it presently he
doesn't think in the past I was and he
doesn't think in the future I will be
because by seeing you correctly that
possibility of mistake of I am right
here right now
he is already his past is included in it
and the future is included and why
because they're all subordinate to the
presence of that possibility
so the mind is still not oppressed
currently possibility of it possibility
of the mind being oppressed by the
unwholesome you could just interstate
with a question for a while as well
because it will clarify the domain of
the possibility without overly
particular izing it so to speak all the
rationalizing it nor mystifying it
either am I liable to being affected by
the unwholesome long - answering it and
you see what you are thinking about well
you are kind of refraining from
announcer tune into an extent he's the
domain you asked about
he's the domain you need to understand
and often the reason what people don't
understand is because they don't see it
because they never asked the question in
the wrong way as a way of establishing
the mind may that's how even Jonathan
Malcolm or Galano in the would encourage
him to practice study his money Jonas
because it would be much least food and
benefit he goes on the nutrient says
first Jonathan on what is the first John
well the Buddhist probably said it's
this is the presence of this it's the
president of this factor that factor
whatever translated and then he was
understanding it understanding it in
Toledo can I do more of this as in
further development of the same
principle yes second third
so by asking the question am I liable
today to the pressure of the unwholesome
and reliable to the pressure of
sensuality malai Wilson shot Emma liable
to be a will and not like yes no well
this means that and overly rationalizing
it or providing psychologizing answers
just by staying with a question for a
while you're staying with the domain
that you did after your questions and
that's how you start to discern the
domain by not jumping to give an answer
but instead discerning the answer on
account of the enduring domain that you
asked about so you could just somebody
can just spend the day having the mind
established upon this question of being
liable to sit unwholesome just spend
your day with that being an implication
of your day
whatever you do that unwholesome you
might be liable to it and then you see
when a particular and wholesome arises
you realize yes this could have only
risen on the overall liability towards
the possibility of unwholesome but it's
not that that possibility has become
this particular one no the two separate
domains so the possibility of my
liability to unwholesome states
throughout the day and then you get an
unwholesome state there is still a
possibility of being liable let's now
also verified on the present level but
you don't you stop caring about the
present level in that direct manner
because you realize that's not where the
problem is the problem is on the level
of the mind and being affected by the
domain of the point domain a possibility
of sensuality will and so on and also if
you become mindful of of your liability
toward unwholesome that in itself then
mindfulness becomes a protection against
unwholesome actually affecting you might
not be completely out of it but
mindfulness or the possibility of are
also affecting you means no particular
unwholesome can effective mindfulness of
the fundamental liability to do come
means a particular booger can affect you
because it's all about removing that you
can't remove that possibility because
it's not yours to begin with
cerio's we have to do is develop
mindfulness in regard to it to the
extent necessary wherever you stop
entertaining slightest notion that this
is pleasurable and for me that's it and
that's often the problem people all
shoot them up they don't see where the
problem is then they overdo it and they
end up denying things i'ma stop thinking
i'ma stop looking at blind deaf man
becomes the goal because you don't know
what to do
you start denying everything yeah you
must not engage with some shadowy
liberal on a particular basis means the
body needs to be restrained speech needs
to be restrained
mine needs to be restrained and the
restraint of mind is truly strength and
understanding the possibility of being
liable to it in the first place
are you blaming the possibility and
trying to get rid of it means you're not
seeing where the problem is so person
instead of all this time I stopped
thinking about it's impossible because I
is thinking about sites and you must
want to feed it that's what we'll say
you tie them in they will be thinking
about the feeding grounds where they
used to go and eaten and do stuff that's
not your problem
the problem is why am i emotionally
bothered by this literally so pressure
of sensuality will arise again in the
future why or will I be emotionally affected by
why or will I be emotionally affected by
that if the answer is yes why why am i
emotionally affected by this and you
realize people would realize that they
would be emotional families because they
never dwelt long enough on the fact that
you can't be emotionally affected by
even if you want as in you can't have it
be yours even if you want to cuz it
isn't you haven't created it it's a bond
with you it's own sin Cara's our
respective senses inseparable from so
we'll need to do is then PO all need to
do is stop regarding it rumbly and then
we'll stop
affecting and you stop regarding it
wrongly if you start seeing it no this
is dangerous so how you arrived at that
regarding it as a danger it's up to up
to up to a person itself with its simple
faith in the Buddha is being ultimately
right nobody is talking about and you
already have verified a great deal of it
she just had faith what he said himself
it's worth regarding in his dangerous
he's gonna have tremendous benefit I
don't quite know how but I'll do it and
yeah that's enough to do it that basis
of faith which was that resulting
knowledge all if you need more of like
the parson and self-questioning
hammering it further fine you gonna
arrive at same conclusions because
that's what the bullet did say he didn't
fabricate like a false advertisement no
so the possibility of sensuality effects
person presently because he still wants
the pleasure of it he hasn't seen
pleasure of it he might have seen how
various sensual objects are ugly
repulsive dissatisfactory dangerous but
he hasn't seen that pleasure in regard
to them he's dangerous why because he
kept looking on the level of the objects
but pleasure is neither in the sight nor
in the eye it's in regard to the to
pleasure of the touch is neither in the
top in the in the tap which is touching
the object or the touch nor your body
it's in regard to the two so needs to be
seen for what it is and that place is
not enough this pleasure don't know it's
real it's a real pleasure that's why I
understand the gratification of it but
you understand that that pleasure is
dangerous so you rewrite the
significance you you rewrite the signs
and tokens of sensual pleasure which is
factual but instead of dear agreeable
welcoming non-threatening is seen as
threatening murderous dangerous perilous
same pleasure but in order to rewrite
those signs and tokens you need to see
it for what it is otherwise you won't be
applying it to the render
they don't mean like with the question
when a person if a person presents a
question so okay currently I'm not
bothered by any sensuality or real world
but can I be bothered
will I be bothered yeah maybe probably
that is a presently recent experience
that probability and instead of jumping
at answer stay mindful of that 34
reported probability that's the domain
I'm talking about okay so now I'll go
talk it walk sit lay down while
probability of being affected by and
wholesome still remains now I might want
to be keen to get rid of it
well you might you might be keen to
solve it to figure it out to free
yourself from it and that's good but
what it's not good is when that becomes
craving for getting rid of it
that means huh you're bound by it again
so you need to allow it to exist to its
own extent the possibility of sensuality
not extra engage moves enjoy D and then
stop the nonstop trying to get rid of it
because that's not a new idea it's like
blaming the things that your dog wants
to eat you can't it's ridiculous that's
what the sense wants to eat that's what
animals feeds on that's just how it
works
but you deriving emotional pleasure from
engaging with that type of food on
account of why that's on you or the
emotional dissatisfaction or a kind of
lack of the food for your AI datte sonna
so you develop emotional indifference in
regard to the pleasure in regard to the
whole sense the main that's how yourself
understands tonight let's whisper before
you stop wanting the wanting of sensual
pleasure by your senses you don't stop
wanting of your senses directly cuz
they're no use to begin where you
restrain them show to create the basis
for the water then you stop wanting
their wanting and that's how you sever
your liability to
anything and also very much and yeah
that possibility of liability for
somebody who is developed is money with
regard to it well it still stays the
possibility of sensuality but the
liability is gone as in you and Allah
you went beyond it the domain of
sensuality which possibility remains
that's why I hunt can still discern it a
human beyond it
he didn't dismantle the structure of I
and the sites as people who taught us
tried to do which is like a wrong view
of a shortcut he went beyond the very
possibility of the body exactly in the
world but he's not liable to engage him
with it hence the beautiful side still
remain sound smell taste touches
agreeable disagreeable come for this
conflict another sensual anymore sees the danger
another sensual anymore sees the danger
what he's seen the danger he seen the
danger in the pleasure and he's seen the
dangering the pleasure to extend
necessary for that liability to be
completely rewritten on the level of
signs and tokens and limiters of it so
now in sensuality arises there are no
limiters of of super and agreeable
beautiful third limiters of this has
been despised and abandoned and
dangerous disgusting that's what it
means now because there is genuine of
danger discussed in it by you being
seriously bound to them enjoying
pleasure of it you don't see it
and I'm saying this because whoever
would try to practice this inevitably
the man would they're trying to get rid
of this possibility as in there will be
the way of fixing the problem but it
isn't the way of fixing the problem is
developing your mind in regard to that
possible that's my main like something
is good to know we didn't even try and
answer the question just formulate it
clearly clearly elected in your first
Jana version of what is first jhana
domain essentially what is the domain of
centrality the liability to sensuality
what is my liability let it in you then
they will be a phenomenon that you might
want to kind of overly define but that's
not the point the point is to rewrite
the emotional significance of it so to
speak so liability of sensuality
why because I'm welcoming it because
fundamentally I do not see it as the
most perilous thing of course if you
don't even have a notion not even a
peripheral degree of sort of recognition
of the liability to sensuality how can
you rewrite anything about it because
you're fully encapsulated within it
that's why even if somebody lives a life
perfectly safe arrested and I still
remember its insure it could have
understood that domain their liability
so you don't be rewriting the liability
as in the content of your liability
gonna be rewriting basically your
attitude towards the liability that's
how you rewrite it significance so you
could say something praxis Riley is
liable to suffering but then he ceases
to be liable to that liability of
suffering as if the body is liable to
suffering none of that
he's liable to death warrant says any
disturbance it's left its own account to
this body these five aggregates until
they break apart disturbance that's the
most suffering can gonna be for another
disturbance
any of the monies the opportunity honors
and even that disturbance when we
perceive
so clarifying the enduring liability to
suffering or sensuality of anything a
wholesome is not for the sake of getting
rid of it it's for the sake of clarity
of it having it in you because as long
as you're mindful of your liability to
sensuality you cannot possibly engage
with insurance in a particular level the
necessary basis for particular
engagement of sensuality is oversight of
the liability to sensuality in the first
place that's real government it's impossible
that's real government it's impossible
to engage with sensuality without having
order to be bound by central perceptions
because yeah it's certainly the
liability of self of sensualities
already perceiving sensuality on that
level of possibility those are already
sensual perceptions if you're mindful of
them don't welcome them dominant attain
them for as long as they endure that's
all you need to do
that's a gate gatekeeper we didn't
realize I don't need to go and worry
about the particular manifestation of it
because it won't be a problem because
I'm not abandoning this gate post high
mindfulness peripheral awareness of the
liability to an awesome